Shubham Satyawali

UI / WEB DEVELOPER

I am a qualified web developer with almost 2 years of industry experience in building web-apps using ReactJS and TypeScript. With hands-on experience in identifying web-based user interactions along with designing & implementing highly-responsive user interfaces. Knowledgeable on best practices and emerging UI development techniques. Received FY23 Q1 Champ's award for being continuously productive and delivering expected results to the client.

shubham.satyawali.05@gmail.com

Pelhi, India

github.com/Shubham052000

+91 8512006924

SKILLS

ReactJS

in linkedin.com/in/shubham- satyawali-815550170

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Professional Software Engineer DXC Technology

05/2021 - Present Noida - 62, Uttar Pradesh, India Tasks

- Worked for (NAB) National Australia Bank (Client) with DXC Technology.
- Built and maintained the project using ReactJS library,
 TypeScript, functional components & Graphql.
- Managed the application wide states through **Context API**.
- Built unit-tested components with the help of libraries like react-testing-library and jest.
- Worked closely with UX and testing team in order to ensure quality.
- Experienced with working in an Agile Development Environment and constantly changing customer requirements.
- Built **reusable code** that could be utilized in other projects.
- Maintained corporate standards, ensuring web pages adhered to brand guidelines.
- Understood client-requirements effectively to develop complex component interactions. While learning from the best of mentors and leads from Australia, Philippines & India.

Intern - Java Full Stack DXC Technology

02/2021 - 04/2021 Noida - 62, Uttar Pradesh, India Tasks

 Worked as a Java Full Stack Intern while learning technologies like Spring, Hibernate, etc.

RESTful APIs HTML

Git & Github

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Great Quotes | React, react-router-dom, firebase (2022)

React-testing-library

CSS & Tailwind CSS

- Web-application which lets user view and add some "Great" quotes with the comments functionality.
- Live Demo: <u>https://great-quotes-8e617.web.app</u>
- Souce Code: shorturl.at/cgiJS

Todo-App | React, TypeScript, Redux, BootStrap (2022)

- To-do list application which lets user create, remove and update todo(s).
- Source Code: <u>shorturl.at/ACISV</u>

Aniyo (Work in progress) | React, Material - UI, Jikan API (2022)

 A portal for anime heads to find, learn about and share their favorite animes from all time with features such as top and upcoming anime beautifully designed with material UI components.

ACHIEVEMENTS & CERTIFICATIONS

DXC Technology | Q1 FY23 Champ's Award (09/2022)

Microsoft | Certified Azure Fundamentals (02/2022)

Udemy | React - The Complete Guide (08/2022)

DXC Technology | Java Full Stack (04/2021)

- Source Code: shorturl.at/hpt58

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of Technology Computer Science & Engineering

Amity University

2017 - 2021 Noida - 125, Uttar Pradesh, India CGPA

- 7.31 CGPA

LANGUAGES

English Hindi
Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

Secondary SchoolEast Point School

2015 - 2017 Delhi, India

Percentile

- 69%

INTERESTS / HOBBIES

Reading | Working out | Se

Self-improvement

Greek Philosophy